"如果还有明天" 前情提要...
Previously on The Big C...
我觉得自己看到了死亡天使
I think I'm seeing the angel of death.
他有一头黑发 还是卷的
He's got black hair. It's curly.
凯西 化疗效果正好如我们所愿
Look, Cathy, the chemo is doing what we want it to do.
如果我是你 我会选择化疗
If it were me, that's what I'd be doing.
好消息是... 你不是我
Good news... it's not you.
-你也得癌症了  -结肠癌
-You have cancer  -Colon.
-原来你也不是上帝  -我的确不是上帝
-You are not a God. -I'm not a God.
自从停止化疗后 我变得充满活力了
I have so much energy since I stopped chemo.
我不想把所有这些事情
I don't want to leave all this stuff
都留给你和你爸来解决
for you and dad to deal with.
你不能一个人教育他
You don't get to parent him by yourself.
-但你将会  -什么
-You will. -What
我不在以后 你只能一个人教育他了
You will get to parent him by yourself when I'm gone.
你的票在最上面
So your ticket is on top.
他们派了人在机场等你
They have somebody waiting for you at the airport.
你的书在这里 他们也已经有这书了
Your book's in here, and they already have a copy on their end.
没有你我该怎么办
What would I do without you
我所能想到的是
All I can think about
我们有多疏远了
is how far apart we've gotten.
在我们剩下的时间里
With the time that we have left,
我想知道要怎样才能再次回到
I want to figure out how to find my way back
你身边
to you.
你最近交上来的作业
I'm a little concerned about the work
让我有点担心
you've been handing in lately.
我有一个朋友 我觉得她就快要死了
I have a friend, and I think she's gonna die soon.
因为我想让你看看这个
'Cause I wanted to show you that.
你能做这个吗
Could you make this
-我想被埋在里面 -好
-I want to be buried in it. -Yeah.
我一直想给克雷格列表一些东西
I've been trying to give something away on Craigslist.
你有什么可以给的
What do you have to give away
噢 我多余的那个肾
Oh, my spare kidney.
哇 妈 你的脚怎么了
Whoa, mom. What happened to your leg
只是没什么力气
I'm just having some paralysis.
我的另一只脚也会麻木吗 那手臂呢
Will my other leg go numb What about my arms
我会瞎吗
Will I go blind
蛋要焦了 老婆
Eggs are burning, sweetie.
你是谁
Who are you
亚当 宝贝
Adam, sweetie.
该死 我错过了你...
Shit. I missed your...
-现在几点了 -没事的 我...
-What time is it -It's okay. I'm...
不不不 我睡过头了
No, no, no, no, no. I overslept.
嗯 从一到十级
Uh, on a scale from 1 to 10,
你有多痛
how bad is the pain
6.5吧 我不知道
6.5. I don't know.
这是... 我都糊涂了
This is... I'm confused.
十级很糟糕吗
Is 10 good or bad
我想"呕"
I'm like a "ugh"
在疼痛记录表上
on the pain chart thing.
感觉怎么样 老婆 一到十级
How you feeling, honey 1 to 10
-当心点 老爸 这里 -你们 你们
-Look out, dad. Here. -Guys, guys.
我以为你七点就给她吃药了呢
I thought you got her meds at 7:00 A.M.
我睡过头了 好吧
I overslept, okay
早上七点是你负责的 知道不
It is your job to cover the 7:00 A.M., okay
现在她这么痛苦
Now she's writhing in pain.
-保罗 我就六级吧 -这样很糟糕诶!
-Paul, I'm like a 6. -Well, that's bad!
好啦 只有四级
Okay, I'm a 4.
你本来才应该负责早上的 好吗
You should have taken the mornings, okay
可是你想要晚上的
But you wanted nights.
是啊 全都交给我
Clearly, I should have taken both.
好了!
Enough!
该走了
Time to go.
哦
Oh.
讨厌
Damn it.
我从来都没去过火腿博物馆
I never made it to the spam museum.
一直都离那里这么近...
I was so close this whole time...
火腿邻居
spam adjacent.
要不要停下 嘿...
Should we stop Hey...
谁想吃不知名的肉啊
Anybody hungry for mystery meat
如果我是火腿
I mean, if I were spam,
要是人们借我的名义在网上卖壮阳药的话
I'd be mighty angry that people were using my name
我一定会气死的
to sell penis enlargement pills on the Internet.
你怎么还笑得出来
How can you laugh right now
我都不知道我们干嘛要这么做
I don't even understand why we're doing this.
为什么...为什么你就放弃了呢 妈
Like, why... why are you just giving up, mom
为什么你不能和我们一起在家
Why can't you stay at home with us
靠边停
Pull over.
我们该做的都做了
We've been over this.
我的肿瘤在变大 我好不起来了 亚当
My tumors are growing. I'm not getting better, Adam.
我脑袋里面的那个...
The one in my brain...
我都忘记你爸爸是谁了
I forgot who your father was.
它往左边挪了一毫米 我才记起他来
It moved a millimeter to the left, I remembered him,
我的眼睛就更惨了
my eyes got all screwed up.
我也不知道接下来会怎样
And I don't know what's coming next.
你们已经把我
You guys have done an amazing job
照顾得很好了 但我不是你们生活的全部
of taking care of me, but it can't all be about me.
已经够了
It's enough.
你很累 又缺课
You're tired. You're missing class.
还和爸爸起争执
You're arguing with your father.
在安养院里
And in hospice,
他们一天二十四小时都会照顾我的...
they'll take care of me 24-7...
止痛药 食物 所有的一切
pain meds, food, everything.
我并没有放弃
And I'm not giving up.
我只是为我们大家...
I'm making a choice...
做了一个选择
for all of us.
我们还是可以期待奇迹出现的
We can still hope for a miracle,
但如果没有的话
but if there isn't one,
我可不想让我们家永远地变成
I don't want our home to forever be known
"老妈翘辫子的地方"
as "the place mom kicked it."
我想要那里有你们快乐的回忆...
I want happy memories for you there...
只有快乐
only happy.
好吗
Okay
好
Okay.
走吧
Let's go.
噢 天呐 这帮人
Oh, for God's sake, people,
如果这是我的最后一程
if this is gonna be my last ride,
那最好比现在要更有趣
it better get more fun than this.
靠边停
Pull over again.
死人要开车了
Dead woman driving.
-凯西-你不能
-Cathy. -You can't.
如果我连一个愉快的谈话都不能享受到
If I can't have one enjoyable conversation,
那我至少也要让自己
I'm gonna at least give
有最后一次快乐的驾驶经历吧
myself one final joyride.
不用担心... 如果我眯起眼
And don't worry... if I squint,
我还是能辨认出中线在哪里的
I can just make out where the center line is.
你开吧
Why not
妈 开慢点
Mom, slow down.
噢噢噢! 宝贝 宝贝 宝贝
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! Honey, honey, honey.
噢 慢点 宝贝! 慢点!
Whoa, slow down, honey! Slow down!
-抓紧了! -冲啊!
-Hang on! -Do it, baby!
老天呐!
Jesus Christ!
宝贝 你看得到吗 看得到吗
Honey, can you see Can you see
噢 太爽了!
Oh, this is awesome!
我靠! 靠!
Fuck me! Fuck me!
噢 天啊 我们要死了! 要死了!
Oh, God, we're gonna die! We're gonna die!
慢点 妈!
Slow down, mom!
耶 靠他娘的! 哦!
Yeah, motherfuckers! Whoo!
凯西说真的 快停下
Cathy, seriously, stop.
停车吧 一点也不好玩
Please stop. It's not funny.
我们死定了
We're not gonna make it.
-嗯 -哦 老天
-Uh -Oh. Jesus.
-哦 老天啊 -靠
-Oh, thank God. -Shit.
好了 大... 大家都镇定些
All right, ev... everyone just be calm...
要乖乖的有礼貌
And be nice and polite
还要...微笑
and just... and smile.
-我去 -这哪里是礼貌
-Fuckin' man. -This is not polite.
我得做我该做的嘛
Well, I need to do what I have to do.
我是黑人
I'm black.
驾照 登记簿
License, registration.
夫人 知道我为什么要你靠边停吗
Ma'am, you know why I pulled you over
我猜得到啊
Well, I have an educated guess.
你继续 你才是警察
But go ahead. You're the one with the badge.
你告诉我吧 我猜你一定最喜欢这段了
You tell me. I bet this is your favorite part.
继续
Go ahead.
你在限速五十迈的地方飙到了九十迈
You were going 90 in a 50 zone.
-天啊 -还好啦
-Jesus. -Not bad.
你们有一车的人
You have a full car here.
照这个速度 一场车祸可能会致伤
At that speed, an accident could lead to injuries
甚至是死亡
or even fatalities.
我有过这种想法
Well, you know, I have, at one time or another,
杀光所有我载的人
wanted to kill each of my passengers.
回的漂亮
Right back at ya.
夫人 你是在顶嘴吗
Ma'am, are you talking back to me
没错 我就是在顶撞你
Yep. I am most definitely sassin' you.
我可以给你开一张扰乱社会治安的罚单
I could give you a ticket for disorderly conduct.
警官 我就是个不正常的人
Well, officer, I'm fairly disordered.
你能给我也写一张吗
Could you write me one too
很抱歉 警官
I apologize, officer.
我...我在想
I... I'm wondering,
你是生下来就这么的被动反抗呢
were you born being passive-aggressive,
还是说戴上太阳眼镜就这反应
or did that just come with the reflective sunglasses
-老天啊 -在学校里你是
-Oh, boy. -Were you the one
被欺负的人 还是欺负别人的混蛋
who got beaten up at school, or were you the bully
不 真的 我很想知道
No, really, I'm curious.
这是超速的
This is for the speeding.
这是...
And this one's...
顶撞我的
for the sass.
由于你的无礼 我们一个月后法庭见
See you in court in a month for the sass.
好好玩吧
Have fun.
嘿 猜怎么着
Hey, guess what.
我正要去安养院 所以...
I'm driving myself to hospice, so...
碰到这个不错吧
good luck collecting on that one.
右边的尽头是我们的餐厅
So just down at the right is our cafeteria
还有工艺美术室
and our arts-and-crafts room.
礼拜二在那里我们有竞争很激烈的
We have some very competitive bingo games in there
宾果游戏
on Tuesdays.
我们会给你配个助行架
Uh, and we'll be getting you a walker
这样你走动就方便多了
so you can get around more easily.
嗯 真贴心
Mm. Sweet.
-新的轮子 -噢 你好啊!
-New wheels. -Oh! Hello.
你好
Hello.
哦 这是贝思妮...
Aw, and this is Bethany...
在我们这里住的猫
our resident cat.
哈 安养院里有九条命的动物
Ah, an animal with nine lives in a hospice.
讽刺啊
Ironic.
礼拜四我们有宠物疗法
We do pet therapy on Thursdays.
你会惊讶它是多么的镇定的
You'd be surprised how calming it is
就是拍拍猫咪或是抱只小兔
just to pet a cat or hold a bunny.
推圆盘游戏在哪里 好像一个大型油轮
Where's the shuffleboard It's like a cruise ship.
你们两个跟我来
If you two could come with me,
还有最后一些文件需要你们签字
I just have some last papers for you to sign.
借过
Excuse me.
像大型油轮 泰坦尼克号啊
Like a cruise ship Try the Titanic.
嘿 放松点
Hey, easy.
哦 抱歉 我的白大褂综合症
Oh, sorry. It's just my white coat syndrome
又开始发作了
is really kicking in.
你到底
How in the hell
能不能撑完一个肾脏手术
are you gonna get through a kidney operation
你现在看见护士
when you can't even look at a nurse
可都吓尿了
without shitting yourself
我也不知道
I have no idea.
好吧 我们把凯西安置下来
Okay, we're gonna get Cathy settled.
直系亲属请随我来
Immediate family is welcome to come with us.
其他人明天可以探访
Anyone else can visit tomorrow.
我就免了吧
I... I'm good.
我也是
Me too.
真遗憾
This sucks.
好了 我知道这让你难以接受
Okay. I know this freaks you out.
可要试着来看看我 好吗
Try and visit, okay
别看那些护士
Don't look those nurses in the eye.
过来 过来
Come here. Come here.
别把脏碗留在房间 好吗
Don't leave dirty dishes in your room, okay
我不会给你收拾了
I'm not gonna be there to clean up after you,
没有妹子喜欢脏家伙的
and no girl likes a slob.
知道了吗
Okay
知道了
Yeah. Okay.
好的
Okay.
我爱你
I love you.
说吧
Say it.
我爱你
I love you.
再见 妈妈
See you, mom.
好的
Okay.
请问一下
Excuse me.
我妈妈真的很坚强
My mom is, like, really strong,
她疼的时候不会讲
and she may not tell you when she's in pain.
我们会好好照顾她的
We'll take good care of her.
那就好
Yeah, okay.
她可能看起来不需要用药
She makes believe she doesn't need her meds
其实她需要 知道吗
when she does, okay
知道了
Okay.
-准备好了吗 -是
-Are you ready -Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
凯西这是楠
Cathy, this is Nan.
我是心脏病
Heart disease.
你是什么病
What you in for
黑素瘤
Melanoma.
要命的病啊
"Hell-a-noma"
我是贺若 是她老公
I'm Hiro. Husband.
我是保罗 瘤的先生
Paul. "Mr. Noma."
这真美
These are lovely.
在我们的文化中 这象征着好运
In my culture, they're good luck.
任何人叠一千只纸鹤
Anyone who folds 1,000 cranes
就会梦想成真
will have their wish granted.
靠纸鹤 别倒抽一口气啊
By a crane. Don't hold your breath.
我爸爸原来带着我打猎
My dad used to take me hunting
就是狩猎这些沙地鹤
for those sandhill cranes.
我杀了一直跟我娃一样大的
I once bagged one the size of my own kid.
我很支持鹤的 真的
I'm, uh, very pro-crane, actually.
我喜欢仙鹤
I love cranes.
真是个漂亮的房间啊
This is a lovely room, isn't it
真是个重磅消息啊
Wow. That's really great news.
没错 通常不会这么快找到
It is. We don't usually find so many matches
配型的
so quickly.
把你的肾捐给陌生人
You're doing a great deed
真是再世雷锋啊
donating your kidney to a stranger.
这会改变别人一生的
It's gonna change someone's life.
我好伟大哦
Yay, me.
我们想尽快行动
So we obviously want to get moving
检查你的兼容性
and select your recipient as soon as possible.
如果你能在这些术前准备资料
So, if you could just give us your consent signature
的同意下方签字...
on these pre-op pages...
且慢 等等
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
别着急啊 分解我的医生
Not so hasty there, Dr. Pull-Me-Apart.
我叫兰登
Rand.
兰登医生 我平常不做手术
Dr. Rand. And I don't actually do the operation.
对 可是你认识做手术的人啊
Yeah, but you know the guy who does, right
那是当然
Sure, of course.
我在手术桌上的死亡率
Me dying on the table... chances
这只是个常规手术
It's a very routine operation.
没必要担心
No reason to worry.
绝对安全 绝不会死
So no chance Zero chance
也不能这样说
Well, I don't know if we can say that.
但死亡率低于百分之一
But less than 1%, certainly.
看吧 还是有些倒霉蛋死掉
See, some poor sucker had to die
要不死亡率就是零了
to make that more than zero.
要是我倒霉怎么办
What if I'm that guy
我就是那命不好的
I mean, I'm the... I'm the "slim chances" guy.
我还在漱口水里遇到过老鼠尾巴呢
I'm the guy who found a rat tail in a bottle of mouthwash once.
好吧
Okay...
在做任何手术前
It's quite normal to get jittery
紧张心情可以理解
before an operation of any kind.
我们可以给你注射镇定剂
We can give you a sedative before we put you under.
有人注射过量 就醒不来的吗
Anyone ever get over-sedated, never wake up
因为 我命不好
Because again, rat tail... "Slim chances" guy.
托克先生 这是个完全自愿的手术
Mr. Tolke, this is a completely elective operation.
你不是非得要捐肾脏
You don't have to give up your kidney.
你可以改变主意
You can change your mind.
是啊 那我不就是
Eh, yeah, but then I'm the schmuck
见死不救的大混蛋吗
who could have saved somebody's life, but didn't.
那把资料拿回家吧
Why don't you take the papers home...
好红考虑一下
And think about it
不错嘛
Not bad.
弹得不错
我有动力了
I'm motivated.
我要在死前学件事
I... I want to learn the whole thing before I go.
因为你觉得自己的生命打了折扣嘛
'Cause you feel like your life has been cut short,
起码你还能做完这件事
and at least you can finish this one thing.
-不是 -不是
-No. -No
我只是想弹艺术家罢了
I just want to learn how to play The Entertainer.
我真高兴心理医生上门服务了
But I'm awfully glad that my shrink makes house calls.
哪里需要我 我就去哪里
I go where I'm needed.
来安养院了哈
So the hospice, huh
感觉如何啊
How does this feel
我能跟你说件事吗
Can I tell you something
当然
I hope so.
我真的喜欢这里
I really like it here.
我充满愧疚 我应该恨这里的
I feel so guilty. I mean, I know I should hate it.
我应该为我家人感到遗憾
I should feel bad for my family,
可我却大松一口气
but all I feel is relief...
知道他们不用再担心我
that they don't have to take care of my anymore,
我不需要假装坚强
I don't have to say I feel good when I feel like shit.
所以你很开心做了这个决定
So you're happy you made this decision
以前是个决定
Because it was a decision.
现在我是必须到这来
This is how I want to go.
这是授权的
That's empowering.
我得说凯西
You know, I have to say, Cathy,
你看起来比以前自在多了
you seem more relaxed than you have in months.
不是我吹...
Not for nothing, but the...
这吗啡输的真像在天堂啊
the morphine drip is heaven.
你现在倒相信天堂了
Oh. So now you believe in heaven
弗莱迪克 惠明顿的响尾蛇
The Rattlesnake by Fredrick Remington...
从毛绒的腿部到马的肌肉
from his wooly chaps to the horse's muscles,
完美展示着所有细节
this has got it all as far as detail goes.
-真是美轮美奂 -你们饿了吗
-Just wonderful. -You guys hungry
我做了无负担披萨
I made gluten-free pizza.
真是一件上品
It's just a wonderful piece to have.
好吧
All right.
男士留着胡须
The gentleman has quite the mustache.
我明白了 你们要充充电
I get it. You need to recharge.
现在是最难熬的日子
These are stressful times.
我出去走走
I'm going for a walk.
450美元 475
$450, $475.
495 有人出价495
$495. I have $495.
恭喜拍得
Congratulations, by the way,
无论谁拍得挂毯
to whoever got that tapestry.
我真的很喜欢那件
I just adore that piece.
响尾蛇由495拍得
I'm at $495 for the Rattlesnake.
数量有限 只多一块钱哦
The reserve is met. It just takes $1 more.
去楼上充充电 好主意
Recharge upstairs. Great idea.
亚当
Adam.
你怎么醒了
Why are you up
-你疼了吗 -不不不
-Are you in pain -No. No, no, no.
宝贝 你不该来这
Honey, you shouldn't be here now.
现在是半夜啊
It's almost midnight.
我睡不着
I couldn't sleep.
我偷溜进来的
I, uh... I snuck in.
他们这里安保很差诶
By the way, they have really bad security here.
谁没事闯进安养院干什么
Not a lot of people want to break into a hospice.
也没人有劲跑出去
And no one's strong enough to break out.
当你还是小不点 得了感冒的时候
When you were little and had a cold,
我曾溜进你的房间 睡在地板上
I used to sneak into your room and sleep on the floor.
我担心你不通气
I was worried that you were so stuffed up,
不能呼吸了
you wouldn't be able to breathe.
我抱着你的小头
I'd hold your little hand.
在你嘴边放一个镜子
I would put a mirror next to your mouth
来确保你还在呼吸
to make sure you were still breathing.
有用吗
Did it work
你现在不活的好好的
You're here.
这倒是
Yeah.
那个神经病装饰是怎么回事
So what's with the crazy decorations
那个啊
Oh, yeah.
明显是求好运的嘛
Apparently they're good luck.
这样你睁开眼
So, when you look up,
你会觉得一切都会好好的
you can feel like everything's gonna be okay.
我喜欢
I like 'em.
宝贝 你该回床上睡觉去
Honey, you need to go sleep in your real bed.
我想你保证...
I promise you...
我在这里很好
I'm okay here.
你可以明天再来嘛
We can visit tomorrow, okay
你要不睡我就不走
I'm not going anywhere till you go back to sleep.
知道了吗
Okay
别问是谁干的
Don't ask me who's responsible.
我可发誓不说的
I've been sworn to secrecy.
不过干这事的小伙子
But the young man who did that
真聪明敏捷
is very agile.
看看
Look at that.
他五点来的
He came in here at 5:00 this morning
把一切弄好了
and put it all up.
你养了个好儿子
You raised a good kid there.
希望如此
Oh, I hope so, Nan...
不然现在在这事上也很难
'cause it's a little late at this point
作调整了
for major alterations.
你知道嘛...
You know...
在我的贴花和你的纸鹤
between my collage and your cranes...
我们绝对是这里最热闹的房间
we are definitely the most festive room in here.
我讨厌纸鹤
Oh, I hate these cranes.
-真的吗 -是啊 它们在嘲笑我
-You do -Yeah, they taunt me.
我让贺若一直做下去
I let Hiro keep on making them
是因为我知道他想要奇迹
because I know he wants a miracle.
他真的很想让我活下去
He wants me to stay alive so much.
我准备好走了
I'm ready to go.
可还得为他撑一会
But I have to stick it out for him.
你真的觉得你已经准备好了么
You really feel like you're ready
对
Oh, yeah.
我是说 当你每天依赖吗啡
When you're living your life on morphine
和氧气罐活着...
and an oxygen tank...
有时还需要大麻来刺激自己
once lived on LSD
然后在伍兹多可跳舞...
and danced at Woodstock...
我觉得是时候看开了
It's time to kick it.
伍兹多可
Woodstock
-真的么 -噢...
-Really -Oh...
孩子 我很喜欢跳舞的
Roomie, I lived it up.
我曾经有幸福的生活...
I had a great life...
有孩子 有孙子...
kids, grandkids...
还有贺若
Hiro.
这是我们在大学的时候照的
This is us at college.
哇 看看啊
Oh, look at you.
你好漂亮
So beautiful.
那时我才十九岁
Barely 19.
看起来完全就像另外一个人
It seems like someone else.
我们都年轻过...
But we were all young once...
那时候我们天不怕地不怕
invincible.
是时候走了吧
Time to go, I say.
我还不想死
I'm not ready.
你当然没有
No, you're not.
死兆根本没注意你
Deathany is not paying you any mind.
谁是死兆
Who's Deathany
我说的是贝思妮
Bethany.
那只猫 知道么
The cat
我们之所以叫它死兆 是因为它可以预知死亡
We call her "Deathany" because she can tell
当有些人快死的时候
when people are gonna die,
它会跑过去坐在他们的床边
and she goes and sits on their bed.
这太诡异了
Oh, that's creepy.
我猜也许是因为它能闻到死亡的气息
I guess she can smell death.
我想知道死亡是一种什么味道
I wonder what death smells like.
他们说中风的人闻起来像面包
They say a stroke smells like toast.
我觉得死亡闻起来会像腌咸菜
I bet death smells like Sauerkraut.
或者像指甲油清洗剂
Old nail Polish remover.
我想在死兆预示到我会死之前
I want to go
就静悄悄地死掉
before Deathany singles me out...
噢 我也是
Oh, God, me too.
在我变臭了或疯了之前
Before I get all smelly and crazy
在没人愿意跟我住一间房之前就死掉
and no one will room with me.
说真的 如果你觉得我要死了
In fact, you see me heading in that direction,
你就直接让我解脱好了
you just take me out... put me out of my misery.
成交
Deal.
还有 对我 你也要一样
Only, you have to do the same for me.
就是 当我闻起来像泡菜的时候...
You smell Sauerkraut...
说定了
Done.
好了 大家伙们
Okay, people,
星期六的走秀成绩占你们总成绩的一半
Saturday's runway show counts for half your grade.
这规矩又不是我定的
I don't make the rules.
我只是按照客座教授的指示做事罢了
I'm just following the visiting Professor's handbook.
嗨 这衣服很漂亮
Hi, fancy.
会不会太过头了
Too much
噢 没有 超爱的
No. Love.
你那本书给了我很多灵感
Your Egyptian book really inspired me.
很好 唔 但是当你剪裁这边的接合处时
Oh, good. Um, just don't lose
不要忘记我们这次的艺术主题
that amazing motif on the hip
就重点在衣服腰部这一块
when you cut into the side seam.
我不用裁这衣服
I can't cut it.
安德莉亚 这里 你得
Oh, but, Andrea, you have, like,
至少剪掉两英寸
at least 2 inches of excess here.
我是说 二号身材的模特
I mean, your size-two model
都可以在你这八号的衣服里游泳了
is gonna be, like, swimming in a size eight.
额 其实我模特的身材刚好是八号
Well, my model is a size eight.
我是为我朋友做的
I made it for my friend
这样她就可以在她的葬礼上...
so she can wear it in her...
穿这件衣服了
in her coffin.
喔噢 我也是第一次碰到这样的事
Wow. That's a first, even for me.
好吧
Okay, uh...
这些别针...
pins...
永远都不能少了别针 对吧
pins are your new best friend, right
直别针 安全别针 双面胶 钉子
Straight pins, safety pins, double-sided tape, staples.
算了 不管那么多了
What the hell Go crazy.
但你要让这件衣服展现出我们的主题
But you pin that waif model into this work of art.
好么
Okay
我不想在T台上看见
Okay, I do not want to see
一个全身挂满珠宝的死气沉沉的麻袋
a bejeweled death sack come down the runway.
好的
Okay.
嗯 我想知道
You know...
为什么你们会在一个
why would you ever take a job
每天都有人死去的地方工作
where you watch people die all day
被需要的感觉很好
I like to feel needed.
工资很不错
It pays well.
噢 我喜欢诚实的人
Oh, well, points for being honest...
我也喜欢你们陪我吃饭
and points for eating with one of the sickies.
这让我觉得我还是正常人
That makes me almost feel well again,
谢谢你们
so, thanks for that.
其实我们也早就厌倦跟对方说话了
Well, we're tired of talking to each other,
所以 也谢谢你
so, thank you.
这里的卤汁面条挺不错
This lasagna you guys serve is not bad.
可能是因为我太开心终于不用做饭了
Maybe I'm just thrilled not to be cooking for once.
你会吃腻的
You'll get tired of it.
我希望我能活到
I hope I stick around long enough
吃腻的那一天
to get tired of it.
这里大部分人可以撑多久
How long do most of us stick around for
这不好说
Well, it depends.
有些病人来到这里后觉得很放松
Some patients are so relieved to be here,
第一个晚上就离开了
they pass their first night.
其中一些在这里住了几个月之后
Some people go for months.
病情会开始好转
Start to get better.
这东西真的不好说
You never really know what's coming.
不过好多东西都一团糟
We've seen some wild shit.
想到这个
Speaking of shit,
我今天还得再去打扫八号房间
I have to clean room eight again.
那老家伙腹泻拉的厉害
Guy crapped his pants so bad,
刚刚还把屎拉在头上
he had shit on the top of his head.
能把屎拉在头上 这也是种本事呵
How the heck do you crap on your own head
还有 十二号房间的
I'll tell you something, room 12,
他们想让我清理拉在头发上的脏东西
they don't pay me enough to clean shit
却付不起钱
out of somebody else's hair.
我说 你看那尿布
I mean, look... look at that diaper.
他就像个大婴儿
He's like a... big baby.
约斯 你还是闭嘴吧
Jose, shut your mouth.
-凯西 -你说什么
-Cathy. -Huh
我说我的名字...
My name...
叫凯西不叫 "十二号房间的"
is Cathy, not "room 12."
这只是我们通常用来...
Hey, it's just something we use to...
干什么 告诉别人你和我们不一样
What, pretend that you're not us
听着
Let me tell you something.
八号房间里那个穿着尿布的人
Room eight, the guy with the diaper,
就是你以后的样子
that's gonna be you one day,
当然我是说如果你有幸能活到他那个年纪
if you're lucky enough to live that long.
总有一天你也会坐着等死
All of us, the dying ones, you're gonna be us.
我们这些将死之人也都健康地活过
We used to be you.
西姆巴 这就是生命交替的方式
It's the circle of life, Simba.
是的 现在我是快要死了
I'm gonna be dead.
你有一天也会拉稀拉在裤子上
You're gonna be crapping your pants,
那个时候你会希望别人来照顾你
and you're gonna wish someone cared enough about you
来给你擦屁股
to clean up your shit.
等等 让我帮你...
Oh, wait, let me help...
不用了 谢谢
No, thank you.
西得 我现在要借用一下你的照片
I'm borrowing this, Sid.
我看起来和照片上一样吧
I look the same.
嗯
Yeah.
这样你就不会忘记
So you never forget.
我们曾经也很快乐很健康...
We were all cute and healthy...
就像你一样
and could wipe our own asses once,
也可以自己擦屁股
just like you.
你在床上呆了一整天么
Were you in bed all day
应该是吧
I guess so.
额 我饿了
Well, I'm hungry.
你想吃晚饭吗
Do you want to get dinner,
出去吃块披萨什么的
maybe go out for a pizza or something
嗯 我想想...
Um, I'm, uh...
其实我还不饿
I'm not really hungry, bro.
就只要...
Just, uh...
不用管我了
I'm good.
好吧 那...
Okay, well...
我身上没有钱
I don't have any money.
我把妈妈留下来备用的钱都花光了
I used all the cash mom left in the emergency drawer.
钱包在我楼下的夹克里
Mm. Wallet's in my jacket downstairs.
你想要多少就拿多少吧
Just... just grab what you need, okay
好的
Okay.
你闻起来像腌咸菜
Sauerkraut. You smell.
楠! 楠 不要!
Nan! Nan, no!
-我是来帮助你的 -楠!
-I'm here to help. -Nan!
-你的时候已经到了 -楠 别这样!
-No, it's time. -Nan, Nan. No!
楠! 我都没闻到!
I do not smell! Nan!
-楠! -是泡菜的味道
-Nan! -Sauerkraut.
护士!
Nurse!
这里需要...
We need...
你的气味就像咸菜
Sauerkraut. You smell.
别这样 喂 我们这里需要...
No, we just need...
楠 回去戴上氧气罩
No, Nan. Breathe your oxygen.
像咸菜一样 还记得么
Smell Sauerkraut. Remember
你快要死了
It's time to die.
护士!
Nurse!
你就要死了
It's time to die.
你的味道
Sauerkraut.
就像咸菜一样
You smell.
护士!
Nurse!
护士! 护士!
Nurse! Nurse!
护士!
Nurse!
法乐瑞护士!
Nurse Valerie!
法乐瑞护士! 醒醒!
Nurse Valerie, wake up!
快来帮一下我 法乐瑞护士!
Nurse Valerie, do something!
她想杀我
She's trying to kill me.
这老太婆想杀我!
The bitch is trying to kill me!
楠!
Nan!
楠
Nan
她是那么漂亮...
She was beautiful...
那么年轻
and so young.
你是说那个鬼魂么
The ghost
她... 真的 她就那样走出楠的身体
She... she practically jumped out of Nan's body,
向我招招手 然后就走开了
waved, and walked away.
你认为我疯了吧
You think I'm losing my mind, right
不 我相信你看到了你所看到的
No, I... I think you saw what you saw.
可是我不太清楚那是不是真的
I'm not sure it matters if it was real or not.
你肯定觉得我脑子糊涂了
You definitely... you think I'm crazy.
我怎么想并不重要
It doesn't matter what I think.
关键是你的想法
It matters what you think.
好吧
Oh. Wow.
看来以后我该换个说法了
I guess I need some new material.
显然是的
Mm, evidently.
我是说 可能我的大脑
I mean, maybe it's my mind
在跟我开玩笑呢
just playing tricks on me.
这些乱七八糟的东西
These mets are tricky fuckers.
你害怕这些东西么
Does that scare you
你是说没办法分辨真假
Not being able to tell what's real
让我想想...
Mm... let's see.
是的
Yeah.
还会害怕
Also scary.
每天都有人在你面前死去
I mean, having someone die right in front of you.
也许这个体验
I mean, I know this whole experience
会让我面对死亡时好过一点
is supposed to make me feel better about dying.
我明白了
I mean, I get it.
能自由楠一定很高兴
Nan was so happy to be free.
但是让我不断想起的却是
But the only thing that I could think of
当那个袋子套住我的时候 我...
when that bag was over me was I'm not...
我没准备好面对死亡
I'm not ready to die.
我想活下去
I want to live.
我没准备好
I'm not ready.
我不停地看着那个傻钟
I keep looking at that dumb clock,
滴答 滴答 我的生命就这样流失
tick, tick, ticking my life away,
却无法制止
and I want it to stop.
我想要更多的时间
I want more time.
凯西...
Cathy...
我觉得这并不疯狂
I don't think you're crazy.
我好天真
I was so naive.
这个地方...
This place...
带笑脸的钟表 宾戈游戏 还有...
with the happy clocks and the bingo and the...
带樱桃图案的枕罩
The cheery pillow fabrics.
真是好伪装
It's camouflage.
人在这里死去...
People die here...
每天...
every day...
丑陋残忍 让人无法平复的死亡
ugly, brutal, dramatic deaths...
每天如此
every day.
那和真实世界有不同吗
And that's different from the real world how
他得了重感冒
Well, he has a bad cold.
他不想让粉丝们也传染到
He doesn't want to get any of his fans sick.
嘿 你拿了我的...
Hey, did you take my...
我明白你是恼火那个演出场所卖掉了
I understand that you're upset that the venue is sold out,
可我们无能为力呀
but there's nothing we can do about it.
他个混蛋 我...
He's cont... I...
先生 没必要说脏话吧
Sir, it is not necessary to use that ugly language.
你猜怎么着
You know what
打开开关吧!
Flip your friggin' switch!
嗨 很抱歉哦
Hi. So sorry.
你把我的盘子收走了
Did you take my dishes
噢 是你床边的那些吗
Oh, the ones by your bed
是啊 我洗过把它们放在橱柜里了
Yeah, I washed 'em and put 'em back in the cabinet.
你到我房间干什么
What were you doing in my room
嗯 门开着那些盘子就好像在说
Well, the door was open, and the dishes were like,
求求你 把我们洗了吧 我们快要僵掉了
"help, wash us. We're all crusty."
我自己会处理的 安柏 不用你费心
Those were my dishes to deal with, Amber, not yours.
我记得你的工作不就是
Last time I checked, your job was to just talk
带着蠢蛋耳机说话 和我父亲做生意嘛
on that stupid headset and deal with my dad.
没人要雇你当妈妈 知道吗
No one hired you to be my mother, okay
我不需要新妈
I don't need a new mother.
-我妈活着呢 -我知道
-She's still alive. -I know that.
但是众所周知
But it's widely acknowledged
一个家庭成员的即将逝去
that the imminent death of a family member
会造成巨变
causes a great upheaval.
我已经为我的心理分析论文
I've done a ton of research
做了一大堆研究资料了
for my psych paper.
怎么着
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
你还写出来了
You're writing about this
我快要拿到临床心理分析的硕士学位了
Uh, I'm getting my master's in clinical psychology.
你不会以为我要当一辈子
I mean, you didn't think I was gonna
小助理吧
be an assistant forever, right
所以你名曰帮忙 实来监视
So you're helping out here to spy on us
不 不 我是想来帮...
No, no, no. I want to help...
你和保罗还有...其他人的
you and Paul and... and others.
我理解你会觉得受到了威胁
I understand that you feel threatened,
那再正常不过了
and that's perfectly normal,
而且你对你的父亲有些怨恨
and it's also totally appropriate
也是很完全适当的
for you to feel some kind of resentment toward your father.
噢 天呐
Oh, my God.
你被炒掉了
You are so fired.
你不能解雇我 我为保罗工作的
You can't fire me. I work for Paul.
是啊 不过保罗已经三天没起床了
Yeah, well, since Paul hasn't gotten out of bed in three days,
我说了算
I'm in charge.
你可以拿着你的调查赶紧滚蛋了!
So you can pack your research and get the fuck out!
某些想要成为心理医生的人
For someone who wants to be a shrink,
你怎么说不听啊
you don't listen good.
滚啊!
Get out!
答应我你会在秀场上拍照
Promise me you'll take pictures at the fashion show.
我会的 别担心
I will. Don't worry.
如果你想要剪掉这条裙子 只管剪好了
And, look, if you have to cut the dress, cut it.
没关系 我可以穿别的在我的棺材里
No, I can wear something else in my coffin,
比如比基尼
like a bikini.
我很长时间没穿了那两件套了
I haven't worn a two-piece in ages.
-病傻了 -那是你的裙子
-Morbid -It's your dress.
我不会为了那些瘦骨嶙峋的人把它毁掉的
I'm not gonna ruin it just to fit some twiggy-ass beanpole.
哦 我...也许不会成为一个瘦骨嶙峋的人
Oh, I... I may not be a twiggy-ass beanpole,
但我可有个泼妇的脸
but I do a mean bitch face.
那才可怕好嘛
You know, it's an awful lot
就像脸上写着我在便秘
like your signature "I'm constipated" look.
嘿...
Hey...
关于你室友的事情 我很抱歉
I'm really sorry about your roommate.
我也是 我挺喜欢她
Me too. I liked her.
我猜我不应该和这里的任何人有联系
I guess I shouldn't get attached to anyone in here.
我真希望
I was really hoping
今天保罗可以和你一起来
that Paul would come visit with you today.
哦 他超级忙
Oh, he is super busy.
算了 说实话吧
Ah, tell the woman the truth.
他沮丧消极 整天在床
He's depressed and bedridden...
吃着霉菌当早饭
with a side of funyuns for breakfast.
他只是需要一些时间
He just needs some time.
你知道是有原因的我... 我都
You know, not for nothing, I'm... I'm the one
要这些蜂窝似的房间里爆发了
who breaks out in hives in these places,
我还在这
and I'm here.
你的肾脏怎么样
How's your kidney stuff going
哦 桃红色
Oh, it's just peachy.
很快我就要少个器官了
I'll be down one organ in no time.
嘿 安德莉亚你需要什么东西吗
Hey, you need anything, Andrea,
你知道啦 比如肺 角膜
like a, you know, lung, a cornea
哇 不用了 谢谢
Aw. No, thank you.
嘿 看那个
Hey! Well, look at that.
小猫
A cat.
嘿 快乐猫
Hey, there, happy cat.
他们叫她死兆
They call her Deathany.
很显然 她在挑下一个要死的人
Apparently she singles out the next one to die.
她坐在你的床上 你就要走了
She sits on your bed, you're a goner.
她是猫界的死神
She's the grim reaper of the feline world.
好了 呃 再见 走吧 现在
Okay. Uh, bye-bye. Go away now.
别回来
Fuck off.
再见
Bye-bye. Shoo.
肖恩 如果你想走的话没关系的
Sean, if you want to go, it's okay.
嗯 我像是有艾滋
Yeah, I... I'm getting a little hivey.
是啊 走吧
Yeah, go.
我要出去逛一会
I'm gonna hang out for a while,
半个小时后 亚当会来的
and Adam will be by in half an hour.
我会帮你买个打猫的玩具手枪
I'm gonna buy you a cat cap gun.
再见
Good-bye.
离那个猫远点啊
Stay clear from that cat.
在我监视下 你谁也不准杀
You are not killing anyone on my watch.
哦 看看是谁起来了
Oh, look who's up.
嘿
Hey.
我用你的钱买了些生活用品
I bought groceries with your money.
鸡蛋 牛奶 差不多基本的东西都没了
We were out of eggs and milk, and pretty much everything else,
我以前从没买过
and I've never done it before,
所以很可能都买错了
so I probably bought the wrong stuff.
你见到安柏了吗
Have you seen Amber
我得和她再对对
I'm supposed to go over my schedule
下两个星期的日程
for the next couple weeks with her.
可我找不到她
I can't find her.
嗯 她不会再回来了
Yeah, um, she's not coming back
因为我把她炒了
because I fired her.
你怎么了
You what
没错 她很烦人
Yeah. She's a pain in the ass.
她没事写我们的事情
She was, like, writing this paper about us,
好像我们是突变体之类的
like we were mutants or something.
你炒掉她了
You fired her
你没有权利解雇她
You had no right to fire her.
她为我工作
She works for me.
哦 你还负责啊
Oh, you're in charge
很抱歉 我不明白
I'm sorry. I was confused
因为我还以为你只住在楼上呢
because you live upstairs.
亚当...
Adam...
我感觉很不好
I'm feeling really shitty.
是吗 妈妈快死了 爸爸
Oh, yeah Yeah Well, mom's dying, dad.
你为什么不赶紧穿上你那白痴裤子
Why don't you throw on a fucking pair of pants
去看看你的老婆
and go see your wife
我是你父亲 你怎么和我说话的
I'm your father. You don't talk to me that way.
哦 现在你是父亲了
Oh, now you're all fatherly
上帝 你真...你真悲哀
Jesus, you're... you're pathetic.
你不要做让我感觉遗憾的事 听见了吗
You don't make me do something I'm gonna regret, all right
什么意思
What do you mean, like this
他妈的你以为你是谁
Who the fuck do you think you are
你给我滚远点!
Get the fuck off me!
-他妈的 -滚蛋
-Fucker! -Get... get off!
他妈的!
Fuck!
护士!
Nurse!
护士 护士!
Nurse, nurse!
护士
Nurse!
你知道我害怕 对吗
You know this was my fear, right
我想逃走 一切都塌了下来
I'd leave and everything would fall to pieces.
我知道 你不会试着想要杀死对方
I didn't think you'd actually try and kill each other.
他把安柏解雇了
He fired Amber.
真...真的吗
Re... really
哦 天呐 我喜欢那个孩子
Oh, God, I love that kid.
你不在身边 凯西...
It hasn't been easy, Cathy...
一切都不容易了
not having you around.
我知道这你过得很艰辛
I know this has been hard on you...
还有害怕
and scary.
我也怕
I'm scared.
但是我要你坚强起来
But I need you to be the strong one...
为我...
for me...
为亚当
for Adam.
他只是个孩子 保罗
He's just a kid, Paul.
我知道他看起来也许不像 但他还是啊
I know he doesn't seem like it, but he still is.
让他吃饱
Feed him.
给他拥抱
Hug him.
我希望我能帮着你
I wish I could be there to help you.
我不断地想着那间房子
I keep imagining the house...
有你们俩...
and the two of you...
我只是个幽灵
and me just a shadow.
我只能躺在这里的 保罗
I can only lay here, Paul.
但是你可以起来
But you can get up.
你就起来
So you get up.
你要试着前进 好吗
And you try and move on, okay
好吗
Okay
你把你老爹暴打了一顿
So you beat up your dad
哇噢 真精彩
Wow. Impressive.
我大学毕业了 才敢跟我爸动手
I didn't lay hands on my pop until college graduation.
他喝得烂醉 我觉得他肯定不会感觉到什么
He was so drunk, I'm pretty sure he didn't feel a thing.
哦 看看谁来了
Oh, look who's here.
嘿 宝贝
Oh, baby.
你还养猫
You have a cat
小火花 来见见亚当
Sparkles, meet Adam.
亚当 这是小火花
Adam, Sparkles.
好吧 小火花也算名字
Okay. Sparkles
那当然
Yeah.
我想取又轻又亮之意 懂吗
I... I wanted something light and bright, you know
这猫可是见证过黑暗时期的啊 哥们
I mean, this cat has seen some dark times, my friend.
我将它从满目凄凉中救起
I rescued her from a bleak situation,
我要让她打起精神
so I got to change up her energy,
所以有了头上小球的装饰
hence the... the little puff-ball headgear
还有写着公主的可爱衣衣
and the, uh, the baby "T" that says "princess."
他们竟然还真有卖猫衣服的
Can you believe they actually sell cat clothes
我差点在那店里给它
I mean, I nearly walked out of that place
买了个人造毛坎肩
with a little faux fur shrug for her
还有一件我穿的衣服 写着"少惹爷的猫"
and a T-shirt for me that said, "don't pet my pussy."
好吧 你就把我跟小火花一样收养了吧
Yeah, well, maybe you can adopt me along with Sparkles.
那敢情好 你穿那坎肩肯定可爱
Yeah, you'd look pretty cute in faux fur.
我真不懂我爸为什么对咱们这样
I don't get how my dad can just totally check out on us.
这段心酸历程大家都要经历
You know, it's like, we're all going through this shit,
又不是你一人的
not just you.
每人的处理方式不一
Oh, everyone deals differently.
我们之中 你才是狠角色啊
Out of all of us, you're the real badass.
你能捐肾才真是大义凛然啊
It's so cool that you're giving away your kidney.
要我肯定吓尿了 而你呢
I'd be scared shitless, dude, but you're like,
不过就是身体器官嘛
"yo, dude, just take my body part."
说实话 哥们 我也吓得半死
I'm not gonna lie, man. I'm... I'm pretty freaked out.
少装了
Yeah, right.
你被捅了还住在大街上
You got stabbed, and you lived on the street.
世上就没有能吓着你的事吧
I mean, there's no way this freaks you out.
这就是小事一桩嘛
This is nothing for you.
我不会说这是小事
No, I wouldn't say nothing.
这是个大手术
I mean, it is major surgery.
哥们 别跟我爸一样娘们
Dude, don't go all pussy like my dad,
不然我就一个哥们也没了
or else I got nobody.
感觉怎么样啊
How's the patient
喜出望外啊
Surprised and flattered.
我以为进了这地方
I thought you people forgot about us
你们就把我忘了呢
once we got shipped off to places like this.
永远不会 你看上去不错
Never. You look good.
别说好话了 你...
Forget good. You...
才真是容光焕发啊
look positively radiant.
我是说 对于结肠癌患者而言
I mean, for someone with colon cancer,
你真是状态不错啊
you look practically well.
我要吃你的药
I want what you're having.
我确实感觉精神饱满
I do feel pretty chipper.
我很欣慰 谢尔曼医生
I'm really glad, Dr. Sherman.
至少让我们俩人活一个
I want at least one of us to make it,
既然你还是癌症医师
and since you are the cancer doctor,
我看让你活下来
I think it's only fair that you be the one
更公平
to stick around.
好好努力...
Just try and...
一劳永逸的治愈这麻烦吧
just cure this shit, once and for all.
你怎么样嘛
How you doing
这个嘛...
Well, you know...
我在安宁疗护 混得还挺好的
I'm at hospice, so I could be better.
幽默感还在嘛
You still have your sense of humor.
很好 保持住
That's good. Keep it up.
我告诉你件事
I want to let you in on something
也许是不言自明的
that may be self-evident.
这个地方...
This place...
充斥着死亡的气息
it's filled with death.
人们离世 是件庄重的事
People passing away... it's a serious thing.
你说死的时候疼吗
You think it hurts to die
我没有指精神上
I mean, not just emotionally,
是肉体上的
but my body.
我会疼吗
Will I be in pain
我的肌肤会疼吗
Will my skin hurt
说实话
Tell you the truth,
我见过许多病人离世
when I've seen patients pass away...
有时是很痛苦的
Yeah, sometimes they are in pain.
不过可以靠药物缓解
But you can control that with drugs.
可是大部分 他们都看起来
But often, they just seem...
平静
almost serene...
安详
relaxed.
你这么说是想让我好受点吧
You saying that just to make me feel better
我这辈子骂名不少
I've been accused of many things.
弄糖衣炮弹 干不出来
A sugarcoater Never.
实话
True.
其实 死亡还是让人着迷的
You know, death has got a bad rap.
它让生命有了意义
It's the only thing that makes life matter.
如果我们的生命无穷无尽
If we didn't have an expiration date...
-注定一事无成 -没错
-Nothing would ever get done. -Exactly.
还有那些要死前去威尼斯的人
All those, uh, "I got to see Venice before I die" people.
他们就会往后退
They'd just put it off.
我明年去也来得及啊
"You know, maybe I'll go next year."
或者他们能去一百次
Or... or they'd go 100 times.
然后就会说 还是
And then they'd be like, "eh.
呆在家吧 太多鸽子了
Let's stay home. Too many pigeons."
那小船的座位太不舒服啦
Those gondola seats hurt my ass.
听着就不好玩
It just does not sound fun.
好吧
Okay.
死亡万岁
Yay, death.
谢尔曼医生 我郑重声明 你变乐观了
Dr. Sherman, I do declare, you've become an optimist.
不准这样说我
You take that back.
谢谢你
Thank you...
没有忘了我
for not forgetting me.
永远不会
Never.
过会再来看你
I'll see you again soon.
希望如此
I hope so.
敲门咯
Knock, knock.
想吃午餐了吗
Ready for a little lunch
当然
Oh, why not
把果冻拿来吧
Bring on the jell-o.
今天挺开心的嘛
Somebody's happy today.
谢尔曼医生让我心情不错
Dr. Sherman put me in a good mood.
真没想到我能出说这种话
Now, there's a sentence I never expected to say.
我最初遇到他时 我觉得
When I first met him, I thought he was
他是世界上最难相处的人了
the least friendly person I had ever met.
彻头彻尾的大混蛋 让你见笑了
I mean, a real asshole. Pardon my French.
可是逐渐了解后 他...
But you get to know him, and he's just...
真的是大好人
he's a big softie.
他是个又风趣又聪明
I mean, he was someone's funny...
又温柔的孩子
smart, soft kid.
好像给他一个大大的拥抱
Makes me just want to give him a big hug.
我会想念他的
Yeah, I miss seeing his face around here.
他会回来的 我保证
Oh, he'll be back, I'm sure.
亲爱的...
Honey...
谢尔曼医生上周去世了
Dr. Sherman passed away last week.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
谁是爸爸的小公主啊
Who's daddy's little baby princess
好孩子
Good girl.
看到了吧
See
看到了吧 小火花 看到这里多舒服了吧
See, Sparkle See how nice it is here
看到了吧 什么坏事都不会发生哦
See Nothing... nothing bad's gonna happen now.
什么坏事都不会发生
Nothing bad is gonna happen now.
没有坏事
Nothing... bad...
发生哦
is gonna happen now.
没有坏事发生哦
Nothing bad is gonna happen.
Nothing bad is gonna happen now.
没有坏事发生哦
早饭当晚饭吃
Breakfast for dinner.
去楼道走走吗
Going for a walk around the floor
我想走远一点
Oh, I thought I'd go a little further than that.
让我叫护理员吧
Let me call an orderly, then.
他能带你呼吸点新鲜空气
He can take you out for some air.
不用 没事的 我儿子来接我
No, that's okay. My son's gonna pick me up.
我会出门几小时
I'm gonna be gone for a few hours, so...
别等我了
don't wait up.
贾米森太太 你不能离开
Mrs. Jamison, you can't leave.
你很虚弱
You're weak.
正是因此我才要走 法乐瑞护士
That's exactly why I have to leave, nurse Valerie.
我要看看威尼斯
I need to see venice.
-威尼斯 -这是个比喻
-Venice -It's an analogy.
你说不定想去佛罗里达
For you, it might be the Florida keys
或者肯塔基
or the Kentucky derby
或者火腿博物馆
or the spam museum.
我建议你尽力赶去博物馆吧
And I recommend you really try and make it to the museum.
看着不错
It looks pretty spiffy.
我觉得你真不该走
I really don't think you should go,
尤其是没有了输液
especially without your I.V.
走着瞧吧
Let's see.
考虑到我会死在这里 最坏的不就是
The worst that could happen is that I die out there.
我会死在外面嘛
And considering that I'm gonna die in here,
你们真的在乎将死之人去哪吗
do we really, honestly care where the deed goes down
我就是将死之人
And since I'm the one dying,
我说了算
I win.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
欢迎来到双城艺术设计学校
welcome to the twin cities school of art and design
一年一度的学生时装秀...
annual student fashion show...
嗨!
Oh, hi!
艾斯卡 米兹拉赫先生的作品
Featuring the work of Mr. Isaac Mizrahi's
远远领先设计班
advanced design class.
你们都来啦!
Oh, you both came!
谢谢
Thank you.
你的眼睛怎么了
What happened to your eye
亚当打的 我活该
Adam beat me up. Deserved it.
对啊 他就是活该
Yeah. Yeah, he did.
我还从来都没来过时装秀呢
I've never been to a fashion show before.
太激动啦
It's very exciting.
我听说常常有人衣服掉了会露点
I hear sometimes the boobs fall right out of the dresses.
模特还照走不误
They just keep on walking.
你才看不到胸呢 死心了吧
You're not gonna see boobs, okay
可还是会好玩的吧
Well, it's still gonna be fun, though, right
会超赞的
It's gonna be awesome.
哥们 你迟到了
Dude, you're late.
小火花丢了啦
Sparkles is missing.
我找遍了
I... I looked everywhere.
-嗨! -嗨
-Hi! -Hi.
好戏登场了 下一个是我的作品
Here we go. My dress is next.
该死
Oh, shit.
该死 我的模特呢
Oh, shit. Where's my model
快去看看什么情况
Please go see what's going on.
该死的 我的模特呢
Shit, shit. Where's my model
-哦 天啊 -我滴个神
-Oh, my God. -Holy shit.
凯西在这干吗
What is Cathy doing up there
震惊走秀场啊
Rockin' the shit out of that runway.
啊 老妈! 美呆了!
Yeah, mom! Whoo!
秒杀全场啊!
Killin' it!
-太好了! -美啊!
-Nice! -Whoo!
亲爱的 你真是美呆了!
Oh, you look so pretty, honey!
-老妈 你最棒! -太棒了!
-Mom, whoo! -Oh, yeah!
谢谢你
Thank you.